http://amphora-aromatics.com/data-privacy-policy

HomeLoginCreate AccountTrade Account ApplicationShippingSite Tour
sales@amphora-aromatics.comCall Us: + 44 (0) 117 904 7212Shipping
£0.00
There are no products in your cart.
Aromatherapy Oils
Pure Essential OilsPrecious & AbsolutesDiluted Absolute OilsAromatherapy Roll-onsAromatherapy BlendsOrganic Essential Oils
Moisturisers
Moisturising Face LotionsShea Butter/Coconut moisturisersMoisturising Face CreamsMulti Purpose Beauty Oils
Lip Balms
Lip BalmsChristmas Gift BoxesBath & BodyBath & ShowerBath OilsFizz BombesBrushes & loofahs
Body
Massage OilsBody LotionsNatural DeodorantsGlycerin SoapsLiquid SoapsLoofahs & brushes
Haircare
Liquid Shampoo & ConditionersSolid Shampoo BarsMulti Purpose Beauty Oils
Vaporisers
Electronic FragrancersTraditional FragrancersAromatherapy Burner Kits
Candles
Scented 40 Hour Pot CandlesMini Pot CandlesPillar CandlesBulk SizesBulk Cosmetic BasesBulk Wash BasesEssential Oil Display StandsContact UsHotBestsellersNewLatestBlogWhere To Buy
You are here:  HomeData Privacy Policy
Data Privacy Policy
Data Protection Act 1998 (DPA) EU General Data Protection Regulation 2018 (GDPR).
Amphora Holdings Ltd is a registered company with the Information Commissioners Office.
Notice Objective
To collect and use personal information fairly and transparently by providing access to personal data retained and provide greater choice and control over how it’s used.
Who is responsible for what personal data is collected, how it’s retained and how it’s processed:
Amphora Holdings Ltd have assigned a Data Controller, responsible for data collection, manual processing and the protection of personal information. The Data Controller will make information available to its data subjects on request (the individuals whom the data relates to), so far as practicable or when legally obliged to do so.
• The name of Amphora Holdings Ltd Data Controller and Data Protection Officer is Mr Woody Evans, Managing Director Tel: 0117 904 7212
Responsibilities of the Data Controller:
• What information is being collected
• Who collects it
• How it’s collected
• Why it’s being collected
• How it will be used
• Who it will be shared with
• How it is protected
• What will be the effect of this on the individuals concerned
• If the intended use is likely to cause individuals to object or complain
What personal information is being collected:
Amphora Holdings Ltd collect and retain the following information:
• Company name
• Contact names
• Contact address
• Telephone number
• Contact Email address
• Purchasing history with Amphora Aromatics Holdings Ltd only
• Your industry sector
Request For Consent:
The European Union General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), regulated by the Information Commissioners Office sets a high standard for consent. Consent means offering people genuine choice and control over how organisations use data. Consent requires a positive opt-in and not any pre-ticked boxes or any other method of consent by default.
Amphora Holdings Ltd wants to keep its customers informed of promotions on products and services. To do that we need to ask for your consent to process specifically your contact information with your purchasing trends (what you buy from us and how often) to identify who would best benefit from any particular promotion. This very basic marketing supports us both by offering you savings and benefits on products which helps secure your purchasing loyalty with us while at the same time keeping you informed and up to date of the latest in Aromatherapy products.
If following consent Amphora Holdings Ltd do not contact you promoting its products and services for a period greater than eighteen months your consent will need to be re-sought.
You have the right to request the Data Controller at Amphora Holdings Ltd, to stop processing your personal data by withdrawing consent. You can withdraw consent in part or in full, for example you may wish to be contacted by Email only and by no other means when promoting our products and services
Who collects the personal information:
On the permission of the subject all employees of Amphora Holdings Ltd collect information detailed above as and when required under the instruction and supervision of The Data Controller.
How is the personal information collected:
• On permission of the subject in person
• On permission of the subject by telephone
• On permission of the subject through Amphora Aromatics Holdings Ltd website
• On permission of the subject through Email
• On permission of the subject through the process of opening an account
• On permission of the subject when placing an order
• On permission of the subject when requesting technical support
• On permission of the subject when enquiring about products and services
Most contact information is obtained directly from the data subject through methods listed above. Contact information is also obtained from publicly accessible sources like advertisements, database listings and internet websites and not always directly from the data subject. In such a case the subject will be contacted and consent sought before being included in any further promotional processing. The personal information retained is not collected through observation, by tracking people online or by smart devices. It’s not derived from combining other data sets and it’s not inferred by automated processing using algorithms to analyse a variety of data, such as social media, location data and records of purchases elsewhere to profile business’s or people. Why do we collect your personal information: For the sole action or business of marketing, informing and promoting products and services supplied by Amphora Holdings Ltd.
How do we use your personal information:
Your personal information, contact details and purchasing trends (what you buy from us and how often) are used for accounting purposes and the sole action or business of informing and promoting our products and services through the following methods -
• Postal Mail marketing
• Email marketing
• Telephone marketing
Your contact information and purchasing history (what you buy from us and how often) are manually processed by Amphora Holdings Ltd only. Amphora Holdings Ltd do not carry out any automated processing, decision making or profiling of personal data.
Who will your personal information be shared with:
Amphora Aromatics Holdings Ltd will not share or impart any personal information to any third party for processing or profiling or for any other use unless legally obliged to do so. For the sole purpose of completing your order, we have to pass some of your information to service suppliers (other companies). These are - our courier services. The information passed to these companies is used only for the purpose of completing your order - e.g. delivering your stuff!
How is my personal information protected:
Personal information is stored locally at Amphora Holdings Ltd electronically and has secured access by authorised personnel only. Information is regularly backed up for secure off-site storage, and to a secure online storage facility.
How long will my personal information be retained for:
Information is held for the duration of a business’s solvency until it ceases to trade or a request is made to withdraw consent in part or in full.
Your right to view, change or amend personal information retained or to withdraw consent in part or in full:
To view your personal information retained by Amphora Holdings Ltd, contact The Data Controller and ask for an ‘Information Subject Access Request’ form to complete. Information will be provided without delay and at the latest within one month of its receipt.
You are entitled to request any personal contact information be rectified if it is inaccurate or incomplete. Any request must be written and addressed to The Data Controller which will be responded to within one month of receipt.
The right to erasure does not provide an absolute ‘right to be forgotten’. You have a right to have personal data erased to prevent it being processed when you withdraw consent. You can withdraw consent in part or in full, for example you may wish to be contacted by Email only when marketing our products and services. To make a request to withdraw consent please contact Amphora Holdings Ltd Data Controller.
Amphora Holdings Ltd reserves the right to terminate any agreement to sell too or support if any request of change or amendment to information limits, impairs or prevents its ability to provide an appropriate and adequate standard of service using our existing systems and procedures going forward.
CCTV at Amphora Holdings Ltd, 36 Cotham Hill, Cotham, Bristol BS6 6LA
CCTV footage is recorded for building security. It’s taken by four CCTV cameras, two in the store room and two in the showroom on the ground floor of the building where they don’t unnecessarily intrude on anyone’s privacy but where they best support their purpose.
The Data Controller and authorised employees at Amphora Holdings Ltd are the only persons who have access to the CCTV Footage detailed above. No other person will be granted access to any footage except lawful representation in the case of a breach of security to assist in identifying a perpetrator.
The Information Commissioners Office regulates the use of CCTV footage because it involves the processing of personal information capturing and/or recording images of identifiable individuals. Because CCTV is covered by the Data Protection Act, you have the right to see information held about you, including CCTV images which give away information about you (such as your car number plate). A Subject Access Request will be required for consideration to view any footage and if authorised will be supplied on a DVD unencrypted and will therefore be required to be signed for and collected in person.The Data Protection Controller at Amphora Holdings Ltd is responsible for CCTV footage, deciding what is recorded, how images should be used and who they should be disclosed to.
Statement of transparency and fairness
Amphora Holdings Ltd regard the personal information collected when manually processed with a business’s purchasing history to be fair to retain and necessary for the specific action or business of marketing and promoting its products and services. The information is protected, it’s not shared with any third parties, it’s not used for any form of automated processing or decision making and is used in a way that people would reasonably expect.
It’s assumed that collecting and retaining this basic information in conjunction with any purchasing history (what you buy from us and how often) will cause no justified adverse effect on businesses or individuals concerned and is there-fore not likely to cause objection or complaint. In the event it does, please contact The Data Controller who will exercise your right to withdraw consent. In circumstances you deem appropriate, you can exercise your right to lodge a complaint with the appropriate supervisory authority and or seek a judicial remedy without undue delay, at the latest within one month.
back to top
About Amphora
Amphora Aromatics is one of the UK's biggest suppliers of Pure Essential Oils and Aromatherapy Sundries. Founded in 1984, our years of experience mean we are the natural choice for all things Aromatherapy
Contact Us
Airfield HouseWestern Drive (off Hengrove Way)HengroveBristol BS14 0AFUnited Kingdom
Call Us: + 44 (0) 117 904 7212
sales@amphora-aromatics.com
Stay in Touch
Follow us. Don't miss important updates in future.
Follow us on Twitter
Find us on Facebook
Follow us on Instagram
We're on Pinterest
Testimonials
I've been buying Amphora Aromatics products for the last 2 yrs and I've found really great and great quality. Wont go anywhere else now that I've found you. Thank you so much xxAbsolute Bliss
I have been using Amphora products for over a year now. They have transformed my skin. Product recommendations by Amphora staff have been spot on. Gorgeous aromas and quality creams / oils, keeps me going back for moreEmily Kidson
I have been buying from Amphora for nearly 24 years. I started with other companies but chose Amphora because of the reliability and quality of the products. I'm happy to see Amphora going from strength to strength and wish them all good wishes for the future.Maria Stavrinides
We love Amphora products. They are excellent quality, nothing is too much for the staff in helping you and they're all friendly. We always recommend them to friends and family and work colleagues. Good prices and helpful staff .. in this day and age that says a lot.Jeannette Natural Complementary Healer
I love these oils been using them daily for several years. More importantly my clients love them too.Peter Hazlewood.
Great company to deal with all very friendly and helpful and service is first class and quick delivery and of course products BRILLIANT.Norma Gianotti
I love Amphora Aromatics, Frankincense and Rose Face cream is my favourite but there are loads of products I wouldn't be without now.Louise Reynolds
Love amphora, have been using your products for almost 12 years now .... don't use anyone else, no need because your products are fab. Excellent quality!Belinda Gibbons
HomeLoginCreate AccountTrade Account ApplicationShippingSite Tour
sales@amphora-aromatics.comCall Us: + 44 (0) 117 904 7212Shipping
Scroll to Top
Home
Aromatherapy
Aromatherapy Oils
Pure Essential OilsPrecious & AbsolutesDiluted Absolute OilsAromatherapy Roll-onsAromatherapy BlendsOrganic Essential Oils
Base Oils
Carrier OilsInfused OilsVegetable OilsOrganic Carrier Oils
Cosmetic Bases
Base Creams
Cosmetic Ingredients
Floral waters
Packaging/Sundries
Empty Bottles & JarsAromatherapy BooksAromatherapy Kits
Skin Care
Toners
Natural TonersFloral Waters
Cleansers
Cleansers
Moisturisers
Moisturising Face LotionsShea Butter/Coconut moisturisersMoisturising Face CreamsMulti Purpose Beauty Oils
Lip Balms
Lip BalmsChristmas Gift BoxesBath & BodyBath & ShowerBath OilsFizz BombesBrushes & loofahs
Body
Massage OilsBody LotionsNatural DeodorantsGlycerin SoapsLiquid SoapsLoofahs & brushes
Haircare
Liquid Shampoo & ConditionersSolid Shampoo BarsMulti Purpose Beauty Oils
Hand Care
Hand Products
Home Aroma
Incense
Resin IncenseClassic IncenseNag Champa Incense
Reed Diffusers
Reed Diffuser Kits
Vaporisers
Electronic FragrancersTraditional FragrancersAromatherapy Burner Kits
Candles
Scented 40 Hour Pot CandlesMini Pot CandlesPillar CandlesBulk SizesBulk Cosmetic BasesBulk Wash BasesEssential Oil Display StandsContact UsHotNewBlogWhere To BuyAA Skincare
Cleansing Products
Face and Eye Gels
Face Masks
Hair Care
Liquid Soaps
Moisturising Creams
Moisturising Lotions
Natural Deodorants
Radiator Fragrancers.
If you're having trouble signing in to your account, please reset your password.
Log in
Don't have an account?
Forgot your username?
Forgot your password?
This website uses cookies to ensure you get the best experience on our website
Got it!
